{
    "subject": "resource/Hey_Girl_(group)",
    "predicate": "ontology/pastMember",
    "object": "resource/Gui_Gui",
    "human_readable": "Hey Girl was a past member of Gui Gui.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9754006862640381,
            "question": "Was Hey Girl ever part of Gui Gui?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8040539622306824,
            "question": "To what group did Hey Girl belong in the past?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7566229701042175,
            "question": "What group was Hey Girl previously a member of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6904946565628052,
            "question": "Can you tell me about a former group that Hey Girl was a member of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5939906239509583,
            "question": "Hey Girl's past affiliation was with which musical act?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5058872103691101,
            "question": "Before her solo career, Hey Girl was part of what musical group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4194490611553192,
            "question": "What is the name of the group that Hey Girl used to belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4007337987422943,
            "question": "What is the name of the group that Hey Girl used to be part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37761229276657104,
            "question": "Hey Girl's history includes being part of which musical entity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29780206084251404,
            "question": "Which group did Hey Girl leave?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Hey Girl was a past member of Gui Gui.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6955_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Hey Girl's history includes being part of which musical entity?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6955_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the group that Hey Girl used to be part of?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6955_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the group that Hey Girl used to belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6955_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6955_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6955_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6955_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6955_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6955_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6955_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6955_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6955_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6955_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6955_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The context information indicates that Gui Gui (Even Wu) was originally a member of the Taiwanese girl group, Hey Girl. This supports the statement that Hey Girl was a past member of Gui Gui."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Gui Gui was a former member of Hey Girl, not the other way around.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}